{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "86 + 53",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 84",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 66",
      "answer": 166
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 55",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 64",
      "answer": 65
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 91",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 41",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 44",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 28",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 41",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 69",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 99",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 32",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 73",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 80",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 58",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 81",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 71",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 54",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 82",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 72",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 57",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 53",
      "answer": 112
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 24",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 23",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 35",
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "24 + 85",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 35",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 69",
      "answer": 115
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 70",
      "answer": 142
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 28",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 57",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 61",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 8",
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 32",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 84",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 95",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 43",
      "answer": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "52 + 80",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 7",
      "answer": 105
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 79",
      "answer": 95
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 71",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 30",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 42",
      "answer": 122
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 50",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 28",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 68",
      "answer": 127
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 52",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 61",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 78",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 32",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 46",
      "answer": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 52",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "98 + 37",
      "answer": 135
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 53",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 12",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "65 + 26",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 60",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 39",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 67",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 72",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 100",
      "answer": 156
    },
    {
      "question": "53 + 1",
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 1",
      "answer": 56
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 80",
      "answer": 130
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 65",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 76",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 7",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 41",
      "answer": 83
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 72",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 91",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 79",
      "answer": 162
    },
    {
      "question": "61 + 42",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "54 + 69",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 4",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 45",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 38",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 62",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "19 + 48",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "36 + 4",
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 22",
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "question": "91 + 58",
      "answer": 149
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 49",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 9",
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 7",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 18",
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 60",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 83",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 15",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 37",
      "answer": 66
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 76",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 75",
      "answer": 172
    },
    {
      "question": "60 + 56",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 69",
      "answer": 99
    },
    {
      "question": "22 + 59",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 34",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 3",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 4",
      "answer": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 13",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 96",
      "answer": 179
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 6,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 500,
      "to": 600
    }
  }
}